Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh City Council, 1963-2010; 1987-2002; I.
  - City Departments, 1983-2002; 1988-2001; 3.
    - PS/P-1 Police Bureau- General, 1988-1999 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - PS/P-1a Policing Strategies for Ferlo, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Police- Conflict Resolution and Mediation, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - PS/P-3 Bureau of Police- Auto Theft, 1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
    - Public Safety, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - PS/P-4 Police Bureau- Parking Fines, 1988-2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - PS/P-6 Police Zone 5, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - PS/P-8 Police Recruitment, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - PS/P-9 Police B Vascar, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - PW-1- Public Works- General, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - PW-2-2 Public Works- Pavement Management Service, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - PW-2-7 Public Works- Street Sweeper Schedule, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - PW-3- Public Works-Dumpster Permits, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - PW-4- Public Works- Cable, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - PW-5- Public Works-Asphalt, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - PW-7- Public Works-Signage, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - PW-10- Public Works- Electronic Maintenance, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Public Works- Current Street Paving List, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Public Works- General, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Public Works- Infrastructure, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Public Works- Street Maintenance, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Public Works- Waste, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - VP-1- Vacant Property Review Committee- General, 1990-1993 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - WEB- Water Exoneration Hearing Board, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - ZB-1- Zoning Board (Board of Adjustment)- General, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - City Finances and Budgets, 1982-2003; 1990-2001; 4.
    The City Finances and Budgets subseries documents Pittsburgh city council budgets, financial reports, grants, donations, and taxes. Additionally, it includes materials related to the Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations.
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations, 1999-2003 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations Financial Report, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations Applications, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Annual Financial Report, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Annual Financial Report, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Audits, 1999-2001 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bond Refinancing, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Bond Requirements, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Bond Review, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Bonds- Tax Exempt, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Budget Amendments, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Budget Crisis, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Budget Deficit, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Budget Hearings, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Budget- Personnel, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Budget Summit, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Capital Assets, 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Capital Budget, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Capital Budget, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Capital Budget, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Capital Budget- Six Year Development Program, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Capital Budget, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - City Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Finance and Budget, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Community Development Block Grant Funds, 1988-1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Community Development Block Grants, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Community Development Block Grant Money- Budget, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Community Development Block Grants, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Community Development Block Grants, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Comprehensive Pension Fund, 1993-1997 (Box 34, Folder 8-11)
    - Donations, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee Agenda, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - General Assembly, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Grants and Donations, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Grants and Donations, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Grants and Donations- Legislation, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Grants and Donations, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Grants and Donations, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Grants and Donations, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Operating Budget- Final, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Operating Budget- Draft, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Operating Budget- Final, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Operating Budget- Final, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Operating Budget, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Operating Budget, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Tax Abatement, 1982-1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Tax- Non Profit, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Tax Reform, 1985-1992 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - City Contracting & Legislation, 1974-2002; 5.
    The City Contracting & Legislation subseries contains materials related to city contracts, in particular B-contracts and contracts for advertising, bus shelters, and cable TV, as well as legislative materials related to legislative sessions and bills, policies, and acts.
    - Contracting, 1980-2002; A.
      - B Contracts, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - B Contract Invoices, 1990-1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - B Contracts Payroll, 1989-1993 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
      - B Contracts/Prevailing Wage Notes, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Advertising on Transit Shelters Bill's #10 and #11, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Bus Shelters, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7-10)
      - Bus Shelters- Business from Council, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Bus Shelters Gateway Outdoor Ad, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Bus Shelters in Pittsburgh, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Bus Shelters- Port Authority, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Bus Shelter Proposals, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Bus Shelters- RPF, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Cable, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Cable Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Cable Bureau, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Cable Francise Agreement/AT&T, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Cable Francise Agreement, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Cable Legislation, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Cable TCI PA Rate Filing, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Cable Trust Fund, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Cable Regulation, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Cable TV, 1991-1999 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Outside Contracting, 1991-1993 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Prevailing Wages, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, 1974-2000; 1990-2000; B
      - Bill 1454, 1986-1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Business ID Sign Downtown, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
      - Business Improvement District, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Child Care Bill, 1989-1992 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
      - Child Welfare, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Displaced Workers Act, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Ethics Bills, 1974-1991 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Gay Rights Bill, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Gay Rights Bill, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
      - Grant vs. Pittsburgh, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Hill-Burton Act, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Historical Review Legislation, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Legal- Environmental Services, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Legal Opinions, 1994-1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Legislative Session Assembly, 1994 February-April (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Legislative Session Assembly, 1994 May-June (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Legislative Session Assembly, 1994 July-September (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Legislative Session Assembly, 1994 October- December (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Legislative State, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Nursing Home Reform Bill, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Pennsylvania Utility Commission Cases, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Regulation of Street Vendors, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Sprinkler Bill, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Sunshine Act, 1986-1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Tax Legislation (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Tobacco Legislation, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Warning Ordinance, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Vending Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Vending Legislation, 1999-2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Vending Policies, 1999-2001 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1996; 6.
    The Correspondence subseries contains correspondence both to and from Ferlo and his office to a variety of recipients, including thank you letters, complaints and memoranda.
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1995 June- Novemeber (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence- Closed, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence- In, 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence- In, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- In, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence- In, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence In/Out, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence In/Out, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence- Out, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence- Out, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence- Out, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence- Citizen's Comments, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence- Council, 1988-1992 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence in District 7 Constituents, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence In- Miscelleanous, 1986-1989 (Box 41, Folder 9-10)
    - Correspondence in Political, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence in Thank you, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence in Thank you, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence in Thank you, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Complaints/Cases, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Complaints- Open, 1992 January-October (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Complaints- Closed, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Complaints- Closed, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Complaints- Closed, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Complaints- Open, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Doryisms, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Memos to Council, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Education, 1988-2002; 7.
    The Education subseries contains materials related to educational institutions in Pittsburgh and local issues, including the Pittsburgh Public School District and School Board and other nearby schools.
    - Carriage House, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Early Childhood Initiative, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - EIT-School Trust Fund, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Education, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Fulton School, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Homewood Elementary School, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Liberty School, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - McLeary Elementary, 1989-1995 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Morningside Elementary Flashing School Zone Beacons, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1998-2002 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh School District Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - School Board, 1991-1995 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - School Board Audit, 1995-1997 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - School Board General, 1988-1991 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - School Buses, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - School Crossing Guards, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - School Crossing Guard Request, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - School Systems, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Springfield Schoolhouse, circa 1990 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Sunnyside K-8, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Woolslair Elementary Gifted Center, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Election Materials, 1990-1998; 8.
    The Election Materials subseries documents Ferlo's preparation for elections, including materials arranged by Pittsburgh city ward, donations, constituent lists, and fellow candidates during the 1990s.
    - 2nd Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 4th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 5th Ward, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - 6th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - 7th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - 8th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - 10th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 11th Ward, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - 12th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - 13th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - 15th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - 16th Ward, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - 17th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - 18th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - 21st Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - 22nd Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - 25th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - 28th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - 30th Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - 31st Ward, undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Campaign Donations, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Candidates, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Constituent Lists, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Constitutent Lists (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Democratic Party Rules, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Democratic State Committee, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Democratic State Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Donors (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Election, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Election, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Election, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Election Fundraising, 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Election Officers, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Impeachment, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Inagural Remarks, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Old Campaign Proposals, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Election Petitions, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Petition for Primary Ballot Printing, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Political Action Committees, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Election Results, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - State Democratic Committee, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Voter Statistics, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Voter Registration, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Issues File, 1963-2002; 1987-2001; 9.
    The Issues File subseries contains materials related to a variety of political issues, both global and local to Pittsburgh during this period, including affirmative action, hate crimes, street closures, billboard regulations, redevelopment, food policies, gun control, landlord/tenant rights, public utilties, sports, and religious institutions, among others.
    - Affirmative Action, 1994-1997 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Airport Expansion- A, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Airport Expansion- B, 1988-1991 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Bed and Breakfast- Community Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Bed and Breakfast Establishements, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Bed and Breakfast- Legislation, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Bed and Breakfast- Planning Advisory Service, 1984-1992 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Bed and Breakfast, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Bias/Hate Crimes, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 9-11)
    - Bias/Hate Crimes, 1989-1993 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Bias/Hate Crime Laws, 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Bias/Hate Crimes Newsclippings, 1987-1993 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Bias/Hate Crimes Police Department Directives, 1978-1987 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Bigelow Boulevard, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Closure, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Closure Lawsuit, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Closure Letters of Support/Opposition, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Closure Petitions, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 7-9)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Correspondence, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Billboards- Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Billboards- Articles, 1989-1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Billboards- Bloomfield Bridge Agreement, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Billboards- Board of Code Review, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Billboards- City Planning Commission Meeting Minutes, 1993 March-April (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Billboards- Community Correspondence, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Billboards- Content, circa 1993 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Billboards- Copy of Correspondence, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Billboards- Correspondence/Memos Re: Billboard Regulation, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Billboards- Correspondence and Photographs, 1991-1994 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Billboards- Correspondence Regulation, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Billboards- Current Regulation, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Billboards- Finances (A Billboard Study), circa 1991 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Billboards- Charles Latus, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Billboards- Legislation, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Billboards- Legislative Package, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Billboards- Martin Media on Billboard Control, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Billboards- Memorandum of Laws, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Billboards- Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Billboards- Model Legislation, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Billboards- Non-Profit Organizations, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Billboards- Opposed, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Billboards- Opposed, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Billboards- Original Statements, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Billboards- Other City Ordinances, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Billboards- Pittsburghers for Billboard Control, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Billboards- Planning Commission, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
    - Billboards- Preservation Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Billboards- Prior Billboard Regulation Bill, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Billboards- Public Hearing, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Billboards- Scenic America, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Billboards- Substantial Change, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Billboards- Visual Pollution and Sign Control, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Communication Towers, 1995-1997 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Controllers Office Referendun, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 14-15)
    - Animal Regulations, 1991-1998 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Dog Licenses, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Dog Ordinances Letters, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Dog Park, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Family Daycare, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Family Daycare- Fire Safety, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Family Day Care- Ordinances, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Conference, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Correspondence, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Development Plan, 2000 February (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Historical Preservation Concerns, 1993-2000 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Historical Preservation Nominations, circa 2000 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Main Street, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Market Place, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Fifth and Forbes- News Coverage, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Fifth and Forbes- Proposal for Redevelopment, 1999 October (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Fifth and Forbes Redevelopment, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Food Policy Commission- Agenda and Minutes, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Food Policy Commission- Budget and policy Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Food Policy Commission- Mercantile Tax, 1990-1992 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Food Policies for Pittsburgh and Other Cities, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Food Policy Commission, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Food Policy Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Food Policy Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Food Policy Commission- Alternative Programs, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Food Policy Commission- Transportation and Access Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Group Homes, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Group Homes- Fair Housing Amendment Act, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Group Housing Issue, 1995-1997 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Group Housing- Legislation, 1994-1996 (Box 49, Folder 9-10)
    - Group Home- Oxford House, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Group Home Spacing, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Gun Control, 1991-1994 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Gun Control, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Gun Control- Correspondence (For and Against Ordinance 3274), 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Gun Sales, 1986-1994 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Healthcare, 1990-1995 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Highland Park Conservation, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
    - Highland Park Reservoir, 1993-1997 (Box 50, Folder 7-9)
    - Hunger, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Indemnity Issue, circa 1990 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Absentee Landlords, 1984-1990 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Landlord/Tenant- General Information, 1963-1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Landlord/Tenant- General Information- Landlord Service Bureau, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Information, 1982-1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Just Cause Eviction, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Lock Out, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Miscellaneous, 1986-1991 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Substantial Equivalency, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Landlord/Tenant- Tenant Bill of Rights, 1990-1992 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Lawsuit- Ferlo vs. Clark-, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Living Wage, 1997-2002 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - Living Wage Legislation, 2000-2002 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
    - Living Wage Studies, 1998-2001 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Pension Information, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Economic and Industrial Development Corporation (PEIDC), 1999-2001 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Economic and Industrial Development Corporation (PEIDC), 2002 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Economic and Industrial Development Corporation (PEIDC), 1998-2001 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Economic and Industrial Development Corporation Annual Reports, 1996-1999 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - PEIDC Feasibility, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - PEIDC Meetings, 1997-1999 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - PEIDC reports, 1995-1999 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates, 1985-1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates- Amendment No. 1, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates- Amendment No. 2, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates- Amendment No. 3, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates- Basic Agreement, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates- Financial Statements, 1986-1994 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates- Lease Agreement, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Public Utilities Commission- City vs. PUC, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Public Utilities Commission- Constituent Letters, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Public Utilities Commission- Gas Rates/ Constituent List, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Public Utilities Commission- Low Income Assistance Hearings, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Public Utilities Commission- Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Public Utilities Commission- Petitions, circa 1990 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Public Utilities Commission- PUC vs. Equitable Gas Company, 1990-1992 (Box 52, Folder 17-20)
    - Public Utilities Commission- PUC vs. People's Natural Gas, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 1)